That Bharat Petroleum has fallen on BTC,
which was discussed yesterday as well and it was said that there is a
reversal to increase, it goes towards 530
and the staff has come out above yesterday's eyes, a
friend, positive proportion has been seen
and if we look at it technically, then here in the very short
term, the MB target which we see
can be 4848, over tukda ji, when I saw the chart for the first time, I thought it was a
breakout of triple bottom, but after looking carefully, it
seems that the breakout of rectangle pattern is
coming here, it is visible, so it will tolerate a little then
and in BPCL, buy and
go, keep a small stop loss at 469,
hardly four to five rupees below the stop loss,
buy at 469, the
first target in BPCL will be ₹400, keep your eyes on the head, the
momentum is coming, the
rally which started from four hundred and fifty, now more death is visible ahead,
yesterday we told you that 10
global companies are in the race to
buy BPCL and soon
you can see the option on its disinvestment, a quarter inch dark
This is your target, you have to do shopping,
your pick up the scene is 5.15